hypetrak.com 2019-12-25

# Privacy Policy | HYPEBEAST

Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) covers Hypebeast websites, including but not limited to:

HYPEBEAST.com  
HYPEBEAST.cn  
HYPEBEAST.kr  
HBX.com  
HBXCN.com,  
HYPEBAE.com  
HYPEKIDS.com  
POPBEE.com 

POPBEE.CN  
HYPEDB.com,  
HYPEMAKER.com  
HYPEBEAST.ltd  
HYPEBEAST.xyz  
HYPEFEST.com  
THEBERRICS.com 

(collectively “Hypebeast Sites”), owned and/or operated by Hypebeast Hong Kong Limited, a body corporate doing business in the Hong Kong Special Administrative Region of the People’s Republic of China (“we” or “Hypebeast”). Our goal is to bring you information related to collect and use of personal data, but at the same time, protect your privacy. Please read through our Policy to learn more. 

This Policy covers Hypebeast’s collection and use of any personal data which we may collect when you access or use any of Hypebeast Sites and/or Hypebeast services, and Hypebeast’s use of personal data that our business partner(s) may share with us. This Policy does not cover personal data (if any) collected from elsewhere, including but not limited to offline and/or other sites linked to and from Hypebeast Sites, as well as from third parties that Hypebeast does not control and/or own, or individual(s) not employed or managed by Hypebeast. 

This Policy is complementary to our website Terms & Conditions (hypebeast.com/terms). Please refer to the link for further information. 

We may modify this Policy from time to time, so please come back often for updates. Your continuing access and use on any of Hypebeast Sites, providing personal data and/or use of our products and/or services after any changes made to this Policy constitutes your acceptance to all of the change(s) made. 

### 1\. Introduction

Thank you for visiting Hypebeast Sites. This Policy is to provide details on how we collect and use your personal data. Use of our Hypebeast Sites, our products and/or services, constitutes your acceptance to all provisions in this Policy. If you do not agree and accept this Policy, please do not or cease to use any of Hypebeast Sites, provide information to us or use any of our products and/or services. 

For website visitors, app users, account holders and customers from European Union (“EU”), please refer to our GDPR webpage on details of how we comply with EU’s General Data Protection Regulation Policy (“GDPR”). 

### 2\. Personal Data You Provide to Us

Hypebeast Sites generally collect personally identifying information (such as, for example, your name, email address, contact address, phone number,etc.) (“Personal Data”) with your specific knowledge and consent. This includes but is not limited to when you place orders with us, subscribe to our newsletter mailing list, create an account with us, enter a raffle sweepstakes or giveaway and complete a survey, etc.. You can choose not to provide us with certain personal data, but we may not be able to process your orders, transactions or applications, or you may not be able to take advantage of many of our special features.

Registration: To use select parts of our websites such as HYPEBEAST.com Forum, you must complete a registration form. As part of this registration form, we require your email address and date of birth. Please note that if you do not provide all the required personal data to us or if the data provided is inaccurate, we may not be able to process your registration and you may not be able to post on our forum or use selected parts of our website. Optional information such as your referrer or time zone may also be requested.

### 3\. Public Areas

When you post, contribute or share any content to a public area on any of the Hypebeast Sites such as our comments sections, the content(s) you submit will be made available to general public. To protect your privacy, we recommend you exercise caution in submitting, sharing or posting any personal data or sensitive information on such public area, such as your full name, address, phone number, or any other information that may allow other users or third parties to locate you or obtain information about you.

You are entirely responsible for your use on any of Hypebeast Sites, for all of the contents that you submit or post on our websites, for any and all activities that occur under your account, and for ensuring, protecting and safeguarding confidentiality and security of your account. We shall not be held liable in any event for any and all claims, loss or damage resulting from a breach of the foregoing, or your use of and contributions on our Sites, or any unauthorized use of your account.

### 4\. Personal Data We Collect When You Buy from Us

When you place an order with us, you may be required to provide your legal name, e-mail address, telephone number, residential and shipping address, payment type and details (such as credit card details), and shipment type. If you do not provide us with the requested personal data, or if data provided is inaccurate, we may not be able to process your order or provide sufficient customer service upon receiving your order inquiry. We will use your personal data provided to process your order and for the purposes set out in this Policy. In no event shall we disclose any personal data given except as otherwise stated herein or notified.

### 5\. Automatic Information

Our servers may automatically collect automatic, individual and/or aggregate information about your electronic device (such as phone, computer) used when you visit Hypebeast Sites, such as the website that referred you, internet Protocol (“IP”) address, type and configuration of the internet browser of your electronic device, browsing preference such as language settings, font size, geo-location, operating system, and other usage and traffic information. 

Hypebeast uses this automatic, individual and/or aggregate information to analyse trends, gather and prepare statistics or demographic information and administer our websites so we may provide improved online web experiences to our users and visitors.

Information collected will not identify you personally. We may provide such information (not necessarily personal data) to our partners about how our users collectively use our Sites, so they may further understand how their areas are used and our websites, in order to provide you with improved web experience.

We may also be legally required to disclose or provide access to our database so to cooperate with the applicable laws, regulations, court order and/or request from government authority, which we will provide for those specific request.

For the avoidance of doubt, this Policy does not restrict or limit our collection and use of such automatic and/or aggregated information.

### 6\. Use and Provision of Personal Data

We may collect, use, store and provide your personal data in conducting our business activities, including for the following purpose:

  * To enhance or improve user experience, Hypebeast Sites and/or our products and/or services, or facilitate and improve our performance over any of our products or services offered on our Sites.
  * To register, verify, process and maintain your account on Hypebeast Sites.
  * To process, verify, operate, manage, administer and maintain membership programs for our users, including but not limited to the HBX VIP Membership Program, HBX Referral Program, etc.
  * To process your orders and/or transactions on Hypebeast Sites and/or for our products and/or services.
  * To conduct and process any contests, raffle sweepstakes, giveaways and/or surveys that we may from time to time organize via Hypebeast Sites, our business, products and/or services, and to announce the winners of the relevant contests and/or sweepstakes (as the case may be) on Hypebeast Sites or any other medium/channels as may be required under the applicable laws.
  * To communicate with you about changes/revisions to our Privacy Policy, Terms & Conditions, our websites or respond to inquiries.
  * To send e-mails and/or other marketing communications about our websites and/or other news, product, or promotional sale alerts, related products and/or services, or updates for Hypebeast Sites, provided that we have obtained your explicit consent to do so.
  * To detect, investigate, identify and protect against and/or preventing fraudulent transactions and other misuses of our websites and/or other activities on Hypebeast Sites which may violate our Privacy Policy, Terms & Conditions or may be illegal.
  * To enforce our Terms & Conditions and Privacy Policy.
  * To provide third party service provider(s) engaged by us to provide services for or in relation to Hypebeast Sites, to process data on our behalf, to provide information technology support to us and/or conduct maintenance of our servers, data banks and databases, including but not limited to IT contractor(s), website analytic service provider(s), data processor(s) and service provider(s) for database management systems.
  * To provide third party content provider(s) engaged by us, including interactive and social media providers, to provide services for or in relation to the 101 Sites, to allow the provider to host the content on our sites
  * To provide our third-party advertising and promotional agencies and consultants and those organisations or online platforms selected by us to carry out marketing campaigns on our behalf and to measure the delivery and effectiveness of such advertisements (for example, client campaign tracking)
  * To purchaser(s)/assignee(s) as part of any re-organization, merger, transfer or sale of our business.
  * To comply with or as permitted by any applicable laws or regulations, court order or lawful request from any government authority.

### 7\. Cookies

To distinguish you from other users—especially other users on the same network as you— we would use cookies to track your specific computer or electronic device. Cookies are small computer text files that are sent from a website to the browser of your computer or electronic device and are stored on your device. Generally, cookies do not recognize you personally and are not harmful to your device. Cookies are used by websites that you visit and browse to improve your website browsing experience and provide the website operators with non-personal data or analytical information to help improve the quality of their websites for their users’ website browsing experience. For example, we use cookies to save your device’s browsing preferences and settings. For these reasons we require that you keep cookies enabled when using our websites. Please note that if you choose to disable cookies on your computer or electronic device, you may find that some of the features and functionality of our websites may not work properly. Additionally, our cookies may be accessible by third parties or provided by third parties including, for example, Google via Google AdSense on our websites. We do not have any control over and are not responsible or liable for such third parties’ collection and use of the cookies. Please refer to those third parties’ relevant policies regarding their collection and use of cookies for further information.

### 8\. Third Party Websites

Hypebeast Sites may contain links to third party websites, advertisers or services that are not owned or controlled by us. We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party websites, advertisers or services or their use of your personal data. If you access a third party website from our websites, you do so at your own risk and you understand that neither this policy nor our Terms & Conditions apply to your use of such sites. We would encourage you to review the privacy policies and terms of use of any third party website, advertisers or service that you visit or use before providing your personal data to those third parties, and we shall not be liable in relation to your activities on or with those other third party websites, advertisers or services.

### 9\. Third Party Access to Your Personal Data

Without prejudice to the provisions in Clause 6 above, we endeavor to do our best to protect your personal data from being accessed by third parties. However, since we may employ outside maintenance personnel or use third party service providers to provide website, information technology and/or data processing services to us or to host our material, there are third party entities which may have custody or access to your information. Because of this, it is necessary that you permit us to give access to your personal data to such third party entities to the same extent that you authorize us to do so. For greater certainty, every authorization which you grant to us in this Policy, you also grant to any third party entities that we may hire, contract, instruct or otherwise retain the services of for the purpose of operating, hosting, maintaining, repairing, or otherwise improving or preserving our websites or its underlying files or systems, or for data processing on our behalf, or for providing information technology support to us, and/or for conducting maintenance of our servers, data banks and/or databases (as the case may be). To the fullest and maximum extent as is permitted under the applicable laws, you agree not to hold us liable for the actions of any of these third parties, even if we would normally be held vicariously liable for their actions, and that you must take legal action against them directly should they commit any tort or other actionable wrong against you.

Additionally, we may store your personal data or share them with other third parties or reason related to Clause 6 above. Without prejudice to the foregoing, the following is a non-exhaustive list of other entities that we may store, share, or transfer your information with in accordance with the provisions of this Policy:

  * Google Analytics (Anonymous version)
  * Google Tag Manager
  * Google DoubleClick for Publishers
  * Google AdSense
  * Google Adwords
  * Google Sign-in (iOS/Android)
  * Admob
  * Facebook (SDK for iOS/Android, App Events/Analytics, AudienceNetwork)
  * Twitter (Analytics)
  * QuantcastComScore
  * ChartBeat
  * Retention Science
  * Campaign Monitor
  * MailChimp
  * Fabric
  * Google Firebase (Cloud Messaging, Performance Marketing, etc.)
  * Crashlytics
  * Disqus
  * Stripe
  * Intercom
  * Skimlinks
  * GlobalWideMedia
  * Baidu
  * Commission Junction
  * Affiliate Gateway

### 10\. Marketing & Communication

When registering for a HYPEBEAST Forum or signing up for Hypebeast Sites account, you will be given the option to opt-in to receiving our promotional and direct marketing materials and/or updates through the Hypebeast Sites newsletter. If you would prefer to opt-out from these e-mails, you can do so at any time by using the unsubscribe link at the bottom of the e-mail.

We will also be using your personal data for our direct marketing. Please refer to Clause 6 above for further information regarding the relevant purposes of use of personal data for our direct marketing and the classes of marketing subjects concerned. We would use your personal data for direct marketing in accordance with the provisions of this Privacy Policy, and we will not use or provide your personal data to third parties for direct marketing unless we have obtained your explicit or written consent to do so (as the case may be) in accordance with the requirements of Hong Kong’s Personal Data (Privacy) Ordinance.

### 11\. Law Enforcement

We may disclose your personal data to a third party to comply with or as permitted by any applicable laws or regulations, court order or lawful request from any government authority. In the event that we receive a subpoena affecting your privacy, unless there are any prohibitions/ restrictions under the applicable laws, we may elect to notify you to give you an opportunity to file a motion to quash the subpoena, or we may attempt to quash it ourselves, but we are not obligated to do either.

### 12\. Security of Information

We use SSL certificates to help secure the Hypebeast Sites. However, we make no representations as to the security or confidentiality of your personal data. You understand and agree that no transmission of data over the internet is guaranteed to be completely secure. It is in our interest to keep our websites secure, but we recommend that you use anti-virus software, firewalls, and other precautions to protect yourself from security threats.

### 13\. California Consumer Privacy Act

This section is specifically to those residing in California. It is our intent to comply with California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 (“CCPA”). CCPA may provide you with additional rights over our use of your personal data. You may find more information on: <https://oag.ca.gov/privacy/privacy-laws>

Type of Data Hypebeast hold: Hypebeast will only collect personal information that is in accordance with this Policy. In particular, within the last twelve (12) months, the categories of Personal Data which Hypebeast has collected are:

  * Identifiers (examples include your real name, Internet Protocol address, personal email address or other information which can identify yourself)
  * Personal Information as categorised by the California Customer Records statute (Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.80(e)). Examples of data under this category can be your name, address, email address, account name or information that can identify you personally. Some personal information in this category may also overlap with other categories.
  * Internet activity (examples include your browsing history, information on you interact with our Sites and contents)
  * Geolocation data (example include when you submit the location you are in when creating your profile on our Sites)
  * Inference on personal preference and attributed from profiling (this can be in the form of cookies)

Personal information under the CCPA does not include any information that is either publicly available, aggregated consumer information, or those not covered under the CCPA.

**Personal information provided by those under age of 16**

Hypebeast may receive information from individuals who voluntarily identify themselves to us as under the age of 16. In complying with CCPA, if you are of 16 years of age or older, you have the right to request us not to sell your personal information. For individuals who are under the age of 16 years, we will not sell your personal information unless having obtained express written authorization (i.e. opt in to sell), from either: the person him/herself if he/she is between age 13 to 16 years old; or for individuals below age 13 years, written authorization from that individual’s parent or guardian is needed. You have the right to opt in or out of selling personal information at any time. To exercise your opt-out of selling personal information right, you may submit your request by sending us a message at [CONTACT EMAIL].

**Request for Personal Information**

We offer the right to access your personal information and make changes to it. Simply refer to the below for more details.

### 14\. Amendments

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time, and the amended version will be posted on our website in place of the old version. We will also include the date that the currently displayed Privacy Policy took effect to help you determine whether there have been any changes since you last used the website. The changes in this Privacy Policy become effective as soon as the changes are published to the website. If you continue to use the website after the changes become effective, it will signify your agreement to be bound by such modifications or revisions.

If you do not agree with the revised/updated Privacy Policy, you must immediately cease using our website and service.

### 15\. Validity

Severance of any provision of this Privacy Policy is held to be invalid or unenforceable for any reason by a court of competent jurisdiction, such provision shall be deemed to be severed from this Privacy Policy. Such unenforceability or invalidity shall not in any way affect the enforceability and/or validity of the remaining provisions of this Privacy Policy which shall continue in full force and effect.

### 16\. Contact

Any inquiries about your rights under this Privacy Policy, or any other matters regarding your privacy, can be directed to info@hypebeast.com. You have the right to request access to and/or correction of your personal data held by us. If you wish to make such request, please contact us by email marking “Attention: Personal Data Access / Correction Request” on your correspondence.

Last Updated Date: January 1, 2020
